Shahabal Shah

Software Engineer

03065949602

shahabhamdani@hotmail.com LinkedIn GitHub

Open to relocation & working remotely

SUMMARY

Full-Stack developer expert in building modern, secure, scalable, enterprise-grade applications using the following technology stack.

WordPress | PHP | React JS | Java | C++ | C# | ASP.NET | Android Studio | HTML5 | CSS | Bootstrap | MySQL | WEB API | AWS | RESTful APIs | MSSQL Server | Firebase | Git | XML | Gatsby JS

EDUCATION

☐ Bachelor of Software Engineering,

JUL 2017 – JUL 2021

Foundation University Rawalpindi Campus (FURC), Rawalpindi, Pakistan.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

JUN 2022 – Present

WEBORYX LLC, Rawalpindi, Pakistan.

By Profession, I am working as a full stack developer, I have vast experience in android and web development, I worked independently on different software projects for my clients, I am working in WEBORYX team as a full stack developer, my expertise is in WordPress, Custom WordPress Plugins, PHP, MySQL, Html, CSS, JavaScript, REACT JS, MSSQL, .Net Core API development, AWS.

Web Developer

OCT 2021 - JUN 2022

RAXONIC Pvt. Ltd, Rawalpindi, Pakistan

Working as a web developer at RAXONIC. Developing their projects, Have Made APIs using ASP.net Core, pretty UI and admin panel in React JS, Managing Cloud Infrastructure on Amazon AWS, are some of the things I've done at my almost 8 months run at this startup! Leveraged Knowledge in React.js, JavaScript, ASP.NET Core WEB API, AWS, MySQL, and Postman.

Jr. Web Developer (Internship)

AUG 2021 - OCT 2021

RAXONIC Pvt. Ltd, FUBIC, Rawalpindi, Pakistan

Leveraged Knowledge in. React JS, HTML, CSS, Gatsby JS, AWS, C#, JAVA.

OTHER SKILLS

UX/UI: Adobe XD | Figma | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator

Video Editing: Wondershare Filmora | Adobe Premiere Pro | Adobe After Effects | Videoscribe